<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects | Justin&#39;s Portfolio</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/</link>
      <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Projects</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/media/icon_hu7729264130191091259.png</url>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>UBC Lost &amp; Found Analysis and Forecasting</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/lostandfound/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/lostandfound/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This project explores the UBC Lost and Found system using a data-driven approach to uncover trends, improve operational efficiency, and provide actionable insights. By combining exploratory data analysis, time series forecasting models, and an interactive web dashboard, this project aims to provide recommendations to optimize storage allocation, improve item recovery, and enhance communication channels.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Airbnb Listings Analysis</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/airbnb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/airbnb/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This data analysis project focuses on understanding the dynamics of Airbnb listings in Bangkok, a vibrant city known for its cultural heritage, tourist attractions and amazing cuisine. By analyzing various aspects of Airbnb listings, such as pricing, room type, location, and guest reviews, this project is meant to give a deeper understanding of the Airbnb listings in Bangkok and provide insights that can benefit hosts and guests using Airbnb.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heart Disease Classification</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/heartdisease/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/heartdisease/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This data analysis project uses a K-NN classification model in R to perform a predictive analysis of heart disease based on a subset of a heart disease diagnosis database that contains information about 303 unique patients undergoing angiography at the Cleveland Clinic in Cleveland, Ohio.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ingredient IQ (nwPlus HackCamp 2023)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/ingredientiq/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/ingredientiq/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;IngredientIQ is a website that serves as a food substitution finder for people with dietary restrictions. The website includes a dynamic search bar that enables users to input a food item and find possible alternatives, as well as a secondary display that lists out the calories and pros/cons of each alternative.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
